Gael Greene Magazine Collection 1968-2008 MSS.392
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Accretion 2014 - Series I: Magazines
  - March 1982 - October 2010, 1982-2010 (Box 30)
    -October 2000. Food & Wine, vol. 23, no. 10. "Unspoiled Venice." Page 202-207.
    -November 2000. Food Arts, vol. 13, no. 9. "Life in the Feast Lane." Page 176-186.
    -November/December 2001. Departures, no. 74. "The Epicurean." Page 171-177.
    -March 2002. Travel & Leisure, vol. 32, no. 3. "The Best Eats in Hanoi and Saigon." Page 83-88.
    -October 2003. Food Arts, vol. 16, no.8. "Calabria: Feel the Heat." Page 64-68.
    -March/April 2004. AARP: The Magazine, vol. 47, no. 2B. "People of the Year" mention. Page 49.
    -July/August 2004. Food Arts, vol. 17, no. 6. "Counter Revolution." Page 56-60.
    -October 2005. Food Arts, vol. 18, no.8. "Eating on Their Feet." Page 51-52.
    -July 2006. Food & Wine, vol. 29, no. 7. "Insatiable in Delhi." Page 120-125.
    -August/September 2010. Saveur, no. 131. "Dinners with Jaime." Page 51-52.
    -October 2010. Saveur, no. 132. "Great Expectation." Page 52-53.
  - June 2011 - May 2014, 2011-2014 (Box 31)
    -June 2011. Plum Hamptons, vol. 1, no. 1. "An Entertaining Retort from Gael Greene." Page 110 (page cut out of magazine).
    -July 2011. Plum Hamptons, vol.1, no. 2.
    -September 2012. Manhattan. "A Perfect Day for Bananafish." Page 166-167.
    -November 2012. Manhattan. "The Plaza Food Halls Get Fat and Sassy." Page 128-130.
    -December 2012. Manhattan. "The Son Also Rises. Page 131-132.
    -January/February 2013. Manhattan. "Let Them Eat Steak." Page 108-109.
    -Spring 2013. Du Jour. "Bar Code." Page 80.
    -March 2013. Manhattan. "Meeting the Ancestors." Page 140-141.
    -April 2013. Manhattan. "The Road, to Salvation." Page 110-111.
    -May 2013. Manhattan. "A Stella Performance." Page 116-117.
    -June 2013. Beach: Modern Luxury. "Topping Out." Page 92-93.
    -July/August 2013. Manhattan. "One Big Italian Drama." Page 106-107.
    -August 2013. Beach: Modern Luxury. "The Aphrodisiacal Illusion." Page 180.
    -August/September 2013. Saveur, no. 158. "Golden Days." Page 42-44.
    -April 2014. Manhattan. "River Deep, River High." Page 118-119.
    -May 2014. Manhattan. "The Cat's Meow." Page 134-135.